This chocolate fudge brownie ice cream
packs over 40 gram of protein with under
300 calories. Let me show you how to
make it. You're going to need one
chocolate protein shake, some cocoa
powder, some sweetener, salt, zantham
gum. Mix that all together and then
throw it in the freezer for at least 16
hours. Once it's completely frozen, you
can take it out and run it under hot
water for about a minute and then throw
it in your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. It's probably going to be very
powdery like mine. So, what I do is just
scrape down the sides, get all those ice
crystals off the side so they don't show
up in the end product, and then throw it
back in the creamy on the respin
setting. And here's the key to adding as
much protein as we can. These Prime
Bites protein brownies, they are so
good. They are literally as good as a
regular brownie, and they make the
perfect topping to an Ninja Cream. I'll
link them down below in the Tik Tok
shop, which is probably the cheapest
place you're going to find them. Or you
can go on their website and build your
own variety pack and use code FPF.